But are not safe and so on
In all such words and expressions there are also
a kind of feeling or
degrees of
whether something is likely or secure
There are also different degrees of formality
how officially or how relaxed something is
and by reading texts and
thought a little bit on this so you can develop your
feeling for
which
evaluate what is important and not so important
and what is likely and what is not likely
And how can you say it in different ways in Swedish
Then I wrote causal relationships
in other words
cause and effect
Why does something happen
What makes something else happen
Then, for example, one can say
"due
so this happened '
and so do you explain what they are up to
or
“The change
was made possible by .... "
bla bla bla
So this can be said, it's about cause
and the effect and what words and expressions you can
use to describe and tell
about it
Then I wrote logical relationships
logical relationships